{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What is Rick's city?",
      "options": [
        "flip",
        "England",
        "lege",
        "Waterbottles"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "England"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does MLG stand for?",
      "options": [
        "League",
        "Gaming",
        "Major League Gaming",
        "Major"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "Major League Gaming"
    },
    {
      "question": "What was the name of the podcast made from the hog tour meme?",
      "options": [
        "tour",
        "YouTuber",
        "the",
        "talk tour"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "talk tour"
    },
    {
      "question": "What did Drakey poo and Kendrick Lamar say?",
      "options": [
        "is",
        "Who",
        "get",
        "Who is your sunshine"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "Who is your sunshine"
    },
    {
      "question": "What famous streamer has Ligma?",
      "options": [
        "Ninja",
        "and",
        "dog",
        "into"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "Ninja"
    },
    {
      "question": "What key do you press to pay respects?",
      "options": [
        "F key",
        "Ice",
        "Finish",
        "Bucket"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "F key"
    },
    {
      "question": "What challenge made people put two pencils on top of each other to summon a demon?",
      "options": [
        "Charlie Charlie challenge",
        "challenge",
        "Doge",
        "adorable"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "Charlie Charlie challenge"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the weirdest state in America?",
      "options": [
        "Ohio",
        "Ohio River",
        "Fill",
        "blank"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "Ohio"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the meme snack and drink?",
      "options": [
        "Doritos and Mountain Dew",
        "and",
        "is",
        "Dew"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "Doritos and Mountain Dew"
    },
    {
      "question": "What did the Yodeling Kid perform in?",
      "options": [
        "Ha",
        "to",
        "Walmart",
        "say"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "Walmart"
    }
  ]
}